易考范文二十九
The above drawings vividly reflect celebrations
of the Spring Festival. Compared with putting up couplets,
making dumplings and children receiving money from elders,
the traditional customs that have been observed
for thousands of years,
watching the Spring Festival Gala is a novelty,
which has been incorporated into the joyful atmosphere.
It seems to me that the message the painter
intends to convey is not limited to
the Spring Festival celebration;
it is  also about inheritance and innovation of
our fine traditional culture, to be exact.
It is essential that we hold a dialectical attitude
toward the issue. For one thing,
abandoning the heritage left by our ancestors,
if we will fail to keep a foothold as a nation
with unique characteristics. For another,
maintaining tradition doesn't necessarily mean
we hang on to the rules handed down from distant ages.
In an era of intensified globalization,
can China, the nation of the largest population
and the third vastest land in the world,
isolate herself from other parts of the earth?
Absolutely not. Take traditional Chinese medicine for example.
The ancient field could hardly assumed new charm
if it had been for doctors' endeavor
to integrate Western medicine with it.
Generally speaking, only if we combine the preservation
and the development of our fine traditional culture,
can we keep abreast with the times in an all-around way.